const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'The Paleolitic era is also known as the ',
      answers: [
        'Old Stone Age.',
        'New Stone Age.',
        'Bronze Age.',
        'Iron Age.'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Old Stone Age.'
    },
    {
      question: 'The Old Stone Age is from ',
      answers: [
        '3.4 million years ago to 2.5 million years ago.',
        '2.5 million years ago to the end of the last Ice Age.',
        '2.5 million years ago to 3,300 BCE (farming)',
        'the end of the last Ice Age to 4000 BCE.'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '2.5 million years ago to the end of the last Ice Age.'
    },
    {
      question: 'The Paleolithic era is characterized by ',
      answers: [
        'farming',
        'agriculture',
        'stone tools',
        'cave paintings'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'stone tools'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which, of the genus Homo, attained Paleolithic development?',
      answers: [
        'Australopithecus anamensis and Homo sapiens',
        'Homo neanderthalensis and Homo sapiens',
        'Homo habilis and Homo sapiens',
        'Homo erectus and Homo sapiens'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Homo neanderthalensis and Homo sapiens'
    },
    {
      question: 'What economy was typical of Peleolithic society?',
      answers: [
        'capitalism',
        'agriculture',
        'communism',
        'hunter-gatherer'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'hunter-gatherer'
    },
    {
      question: 'Paleolithic humans enjoyed ____ leisure time than those in farming and industial societies.',
      answers: [
        'more',
        'less',
        'the same',
        '(unknown)'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'more'
    },
    {
      question: 'People in the Paleolithic were nomadic because ',
      answers: [
      'they lacked the knowledge to build sturdy houses.',
      'they were bored and wanted to see the world.',
      'they followed herds of animals to aquire food.',
      'it was advatageous relative to other hominins.'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'they followed herds of animals to aquire food.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Homo neanderthalensis were extinct by the end of the Paleolitic but we have traces of their DNA because ',
      answers: [
        'we are their descendants.',
        'we interbred while coexisting.',
        'there were similar genetic mutations.',
        'of God; He decided to.'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'we interbred while coexisting.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Evidence for the widespread use of language includes ',
      answers: [
      'evidence of collaboration between different groups.',
      'various written inscriptions found at Paleolithic sites.',
      'long-distance travel and trade, and organizational structures.',
      'the ability to hunt animals for food and then share it.'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'long-distance travel and trade, and organizational structures.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What marked the end of the Paleolithic era and the beginning of the Mesolithic era?',
      answers: [
        'The beginning of agriculture.',
        'The extinction of most humans.',
        'The introduction of complex tools.',
        'The end of the last Ice Age.'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'The end of the last Ice Age.'
    }
];